

50 Randall Avenue • Woodlyn, PA 19094 • Phone: 610-659-2804 • E-Mail: smg@grahamgraphics.net

PROFILE:

I am a web and graphic designer based in Woodlyn, Pennsylvania. I have worked on a variety of projects both large and small for educational institutions, small businesses, community-based organizations and entrepreneurs. These opportunities have allowed me to learn new things and grow as a designer and person. I am highly motivated and self-driven and work well alone but also with others because communication and collaboration can lead to great ideas. I do prefer remote work but I am willing to come into an office environment as needed to meet and collaborate with other team members.

EDUCATION:

Penn LPS Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp The Coding Boot Camp is offered through the University of Pennsylvania College of Liberal and Professional Studies in collaboration with Trilogy Education Services, a 2U, Inc. brand.	Currently enrolled
Manna Bible Institute - Chester Campus	2016
Professional Career Development Institute, PCDI Website Design Certification Program	2005
Johnson C. Smith University - Charlotte, NC BA - Political Science w/ International Affairs Concentration Honors College Program. Cum laude	1997

SKILLS - Proficient in a variety of computer applications on both PC and Mac platforms:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- Node.js
- Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Fireworks, Illustrator, Flash, Adobe Acrobat Professional
- Microsoft Office Suite Word, Excel, Publisher, and Power Point
- 15+ years in Program Coordination
- Excellent Interpersonal Communication
- Travel abroad experience



50 Randall Avenue • Woodlyn, PA 19094 • Phone: 610-659-2804 • E-Mail: smg@grahamgraphics.net

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

2016 - PRESENT

TEMP - DIVISION OF ENDOCRINOLOGY, DIABETES, & METABOLISM

- Re-design, update and maintain websites for The Institute for Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism (IDOM), Penn Medicine Academic website and several laboratories within the division.
- Design print materials including flyers, posters, event programs, and rack cards for division events and special programs

GRAHAM GRAPHICS PRESIDENT AND C.E.O.

2003 - PRESENT

- Website Development for educational institutions, community-based organizations, and entrepreneurs.
- Graphic design and print materials including business cards, letterhead, flyers, posters, event programs, banners, book covers, invitations and T-shirts.

University of Pennsylvania 2003 – 2016 Web and Program Coordinator - Division of Endocrinology, Diabetes, & Metabolism

- Design, update and maintain websites for The Institute for Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism (IDOM), Penn Diabetes and Research Center (DRC), and several laboratories within the division.
- Design print materials including flyers, posters, event programs, and rack cards for division events and special programs
- Provide Executive level administrative support for Associate Chief of the Division of Endocrinology, Diabetes and Metabolism
- Coordinate all aspects of the ACGME accredited Endocrinology Fellowship Training Program
- Coordinate annual John G. Haddad Memorial Lecture



50 Randall Avenue • Woodlyn, PA 19094 • Phone: 610-659-2804 • E-Mail: smg@grahamgraphics.net

 Coordinate weekly Clinical Case Conference and Grand Rounds Series for Continuing Medical Education certification and credits

Unique Advantage Resourcing

2003

Admin Coordinator - Division of Endocrinology, Diabetes, & Metabolism

- Provided administrative support for Associate Chief of Clinical Affairs
- Provided support for 2 physician scientists
- Updated and Maintained division web site
- Collected data for Penn Diabetes Center web site
- Coordinated weekly Clinical Case Conferences

Unique Advantage Resourcing

2003

Administrative Assistant to Senior Executive Director, School of Medicine Administration

- Scheduled and Maintained Calendar using Corporate Time (Oracle)
- Maintained and updated Database using File Maker Pro
- Performed office duties including-answering phones, faxing, e-mail correspondence
- Special projects as assigned

Johns Hopkins University, Bloomberg School of Public Health

1999 - 2002

Sr. Program Coordinator. Fogarty AIDS International Training and Research Program.

- Coordinated 4 week Fogarty Summer Program and Medical Informatics Program
- Processed / Monitored degree applications and Advanced Research Training Proposals
- Provided pre-arrival, arrival and ongoing orientation to trainees for program, intercultural and immigration matters
- Processed financial documents including check requisitions, wire transfers, travel and credit card reimbursements
- Assisted in grant and report preparation, located and compiled information and formatted reports, graphs, tables, and records

Johns Hopkins University Center for Communication Programs *Program Assistant in the Africa Division*

1997 - 1999

- Organized/Coordinated the first International Conference on Men's Participation in Reproductive Health for Francophone Africa
- Facilitation of selection and follow up with conference participants
- Assisted in the distribution, collection, and analysis of Challenge CUP questionnaire



50 Randall Avenue • Woodlyn, PA 19094 • Phone: 610-659-2804 • E-Mail: smg@grahamgraphics.net

- Assisted in the procurement of training materials for the Challenge CUP Initiative
- Assisted in production of print IEC materials from the US
- Assisted in the planning and implementation of Congressman Elijah Cummings Africa trip, as a Goodwill Ambassador for the Challenge CUP Initiative
- · Assisted in the production of media packets

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT:

Community Baptist Church, Chester, PA

2010 - Present

- Associate Minister
- President of the Ministerial Staff
- Developed curriculum and teach Building a Firm Foundation Class
- Teach Bible Study on Wednesday evenings
- Vacation Bible School teacher
- Volunteer at the weekly after school program

Bread of Life at the Cathedral Church Minister of Public Relations & Outreach

2000 - 2002

- Organized and Coordinated all outreach programs and activities
- Organized Community outreach events including conferences and workshops
- Organized Political Forums with various levels of government officials from the local, state, and federal levels
- Designed and distributed Public Service Announcements to radio, newspaper, and television stations to advertise community events
- Developed ministry database and spreadsheets for events and membership
- Designed all flyers, postcards, weekly bulletins, and materials for distribution at events

Darneal Johnson Ministries Executive Assistant

2001 - 2002

- Scheduled and maintained calendar for C.E.O.
- Coordinated meetings with Political, Community, and Civic Leaders
- Represented C.E.O. at various political and community events
- Performed administrative office duties including answering phones, faxing, e-mail, and responding to inquiries
- Developed and maintained contact list of other ministries, supporters, and friends of the ministry
- Collected and recorded tuition payments for and maintained financial records



50 Randall Avenue • Woodlyn, PA 19094 • Phone: 610-659-2804 • E-Mail: smg@grahamgraphics.net

Harambe Baptist Church, Philadelphia, PA

1994 - 1995

- Traveled to Senegal and Gambia with Inner City and Africa Ministries (ICAM)
- Delivered medical supplies and treatment to local communities
- Developed relationships with ICAM members and supporters
- Strengthened existing ministries and personnel in Thies and Barra Villages
- Planned additional outreach activities and community interventions
- Served on strategic planning committee and initial board member for the Christian GEMS Christians Globally Effecting Missions Strategy
- Attended and helped coordinate Global Missions Conferences in various locations around Philadelphia
- Presented at conferences and workshops about missions and needs of people throughout the 10/40 window

AWARDS:

- United States Achievement Academy Award
- Alliance Française de Charlotte Award for French
- Charlotte World Trade Association Scholarship
- National Dean's List
- All American Scholar
- Who's Who Among Colleges and Universities

AFFILIATIONS:

- Omega Psi Phi Fraternity, Inc.
- International Webmaster's Association
- Alpha Lambda Delta Honor Society

REFERENCES:

Available upon request